<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
	<channel>
		<item>
			<g:id>152</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Classic Royal Blue Long Sleeve Polo T-Shirt]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Stay effortlessly stylish with this Classic Royal Blue Long Sleeve Polo T-Shirt. Crafted from a soft, breathable cotton blend, it offers all-day comfort with a sleek collar and white piping detail. Perfect for casual, office, or weekend wear, this versatile polo adds a refined touch to any look.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Personalised Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/shop-classic-royal-blue-long-sleeve-polo-t-shirt-at-thegiftara-premium-fabric-stylish-fit-and-perfect-for-corporate-wear-events-and-gifting/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/t-shart23.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>300.00INR</g:price>
			<sale_price>260.00INR</sale_price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/t-shart22.jpg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/t-shart21.jpg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/t-shart23.jpg]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>154</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Slim Fit Chinos]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Elevate your everyday style with these Slim Fit Chinos, designed for a modern and polished look. Crafted from a premium cotton stretch fabric, they offer exceptional comfort, flexibility, and durability. The tailored slim fit enhances your silhouette, making them perfect for both casual and semi-formal occasions. Pair them with shirts, polos, or tees for a smart and versatile outfit that transitions effortlessly from work to weekend.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Personalised Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/slim-fit-chinos/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/t-shart12.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>500.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/t-shart2.webp,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/t-shart11.jpg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/t-shart12.jpg]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>157</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Cotton Crew Neck Tee]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Stay cool and comfortable with this Cotton Crew Neck Tee, made from 100% soft, breathable cotton. Featuring a classic crew neck and regular fit, it’s perfect for everyday wear—easy to style, durable, and effortlessly versatile for any occasion.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Personalised Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/cotton-crew-neck-tee/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/t-shart11.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>300.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/t-shart11.jpg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/t-shart1-1.webp,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/t-shart2-1.webp]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>158</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Cotton Crew Neck Tee]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Stay effortlessly casual with this Cotton Crew Neck Tee, crafted from 100% premium cotton for superior softness and breathability. Designed with a classic crew neckline and a comfortable regular fit, it’s perfect for everyday wear, whether at home, work, or on the go. Easy to pair with jeans, shorts, or chinos, this versatile tee is a timeless wardrobe essential for a clean, relaxed look.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Personalised Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/cotton-crew-neck-tee-2/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/2.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>200.00INR</g:price>
			<sale_price>120.00INR</sale_price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/3.jpg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/2.jpg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/1.jpg]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>160</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[The Exceutive Essential Set]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Make your gifting truly special with The Executive Essentials Set, an elegant and functional combo designed for professionals, corporate employees, students, and all gifting occasions. This premium set blends utility, sophistication, and personalization, making it an ideal choice for both personal and professional gifting.

Crafted with meticulous attention to detail, this luxurious gift box includes five thoughtfully chosen accessories — a classic diary, stainless steel temperature bottle, coffee mug, premium pen, and metal keychain. Each item can be custom-engraved with a name, logo, or message, creating a memorable keepsake that reflects appreciation and style.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Corporate Gift Hampers &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/formal-button-up-shirt/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/4.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>200.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/7.jpg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/6.jpg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/5.jpg]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>237</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Smiley Star of the Week Badges]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Recognize achievements and spread positivity with the Star of the Week Badges! Featuring a bright smiley design and easy-to-pin clasp, these durable, reusable badges are perfect for schools, offices, and events to celebrate effort, good behavior, or outstanding performance.
Celebrate achievements and encourage positive behavior with the Star of the Week Badges, a fun and engaging way to recognize effort, good conduct, or exceptional performance. Designed for schools, offices, clubs, and events, these badges add a cheerful touch while motivating students, employees, or participants to strive for excellence.

Crafted from durable, high-quality materials, the badges are built to last and can be reused multiple times, making them a practical choice for ongoing reward programs. The bright and vibrant smiley design instantly draws attention and spreads positivity, while the easy-to-use safety pin clasp ensures they can be securely attached to uniforms, shirts, bags, or lanyards without causing damage.

Whether you’re a teacher recognizing outstanding students, a manager appreciating team performance, or an event organizer highlighting achievements, these badges make every “star” feel valued and proud.

Key Features:

Design: Colorful and cheerful smiley motif for instant appeal

Attachment: Simple safety clasp for easy pinning

Durability: Strong and reusable for long-term use

Ideal For: Schools, teachers, student reward programs, office recognition, or event giveaways

&nbsp;

Make recognition fun and memorable with the Star of the Week Badges, helping individuals shine while boosting confidence and motivation.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Personalised Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/smiley-star-of-the-week-badges/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/badgs.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>50.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/badgs.png]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>239</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[BlueTote Everyday Sling]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Stay organized and stylish with the BlueTote Everyday Sling, crafted from premium denim in a classic jean blue shade. This lightweight and durable crossbody bag features a spacious main compartment with inner pockets, a secure flap closure, and an adjustable shoulder strap for a comfortable fit. Perfect for college, work, travel, shopping, or daily outings, it combines practicality with effortless style, making it an ideal companion for your everyday adventures.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Personalised Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 1000-1500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/personalised-satchel-crossbody-bag-jeans-blue/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/personalised-satchel-crossbody-bag-jeans-blue-518658-scaled.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>1500.00INR</g:price>
			<sale_price>1200.00INR</sale_price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/personalised-satchel-crossbody-bag-jeans-blue-518658-scaled.jpg]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>241</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[NY Heritage Cap]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Elevate your everyday style with the CityVibe New York Street Cap, a perfect mix of comfort, durability, and urban fashion. Made from high-quality cotton fabric, this lightweight and breathable cap keeps you cool and comfortable all day long. The bold embroidered New York logo on the front adds a trendy streetwear touch, while the curved brim provides classic sporty vibes and sun protection. With an adjustable strap at the back, it offers a secure and customized fit for all head sizes. Whether you’re heading out for a casual outing, a workout session, or simply want to complete your everyday look, this versatile cap is the ideal choice to add effortless style and confidence to any outfit.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Personalised Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/latest-cotton-caps/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/caps.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>300.00INR</g:price>
			<sale_price>250.00INR</sale_price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/caps.jpg]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>246</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[The Heritage Tea Box]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Our  Heritage Tea Box  delivers a delightful blend of taste and wellness. Inspired by the periwinkle (sadabahaar) flower—symbolizing vitality and timeless beauty—this refreshing hamper is perfect for every season. Start your day with a revitalizing honey lemonade to boost metabolism, enjoy a nutty sattu protein drink to enhance daily nutrition, or impress your guests with natural honey-based fruity cocktails and wholesome nutty smoothies. With the  Heritage Tea Box , every sip is a celebration of health and flavor.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Premium Products &gt; All</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/luxury-gifting-box/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/gg.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>3000.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/gg.jpg]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>250</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Cocktail Hour]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Cocktail Hour is an elegant gift set designed to make every celebration or special occasion memorable. It includes beautifully handcrafted brass-finish bar accessories such as a corkscrew, strainer, opener, and stirrer — all neatly packed in a luxurious gift box. The set also comes with a pack of whiskey rocks, making it perfect for cocktail lovers or as a stylish premium gift for birthdays, parties, or corporate events.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Premium Products &gt; All &gt; Budget 1500-2000</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/cocktail-hour/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/ggg.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>2000.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/ggg.jpg]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>251</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[SustainElite Corporate Hamper]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This Premium Corporate Gift Set blends elegance with sustainability — ideal for professionals, clients, and employees. It includes an eco bottle with a bamboo lid, a wooden perpetual calendar, a premium tea/coffee jar, and a bamboo pen with case — all beautifully packed in a minimalist, eco-friendly gift box. Perfect for corporate gifting, employee appreciation, and festive occasions.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Premium Products &gt; All &gt; Budget 1000-1500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/premium-sustainable-gift-box-2/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/2.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>1600.00INR</g:price>
			<sale_price>1400.00INR</sale_price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/1.jpg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/2.jpg]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>429</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Floral Print Personalized Leather Diary]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The Floral Print Personalized Leather Diary combines elegance and practicality, featuring a beautiful floral design on a premium leather cover. Perfect for writing, planning, or journaling, it offers smooth, high-quality pages and can be personalized with your name or logo for a unique touch. Ideal for gifting to employees, clients, or loved ones, this stylish diary adds charm and sophistication to everyday note-taking.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Personalised Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/floral-print-personalized-leather-diary/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/p-floral-print-personalized-leather-diary-275464-m.webp]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>200.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/p-floral-print-personalized-leather-diary-275464-1.png,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/p-floral-print-personalized-leather-diary-275464-2.webp,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/p-floral-print-personalized-leather-diary-275464-3.webp,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/p-floral-print-personalized-leather-diary-275464-m.webp]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>434</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Success Achieved New Year Gift Set]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Celebrate new beginnings with this thoughtful and inspiring New Year Gift Set, specially curated to spread positivity and motivation among employees, clients, and loved ones. This elegant combo includes a premium notebook or diary to plan success, a stylish keychain for everyday use, a delicious chocolate bar for a sweet start, and a motivational greeting card with the message “Something New Every Day.” Beautifully packed in a compact festive gift box with a New Year tag, it’s perfect for corporate gifting, employee appreciation, or personal celebrations, offering a memorable way to inspire productivity, happiness, and new opportunities in the year ahead.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/success-achieved-new-year-gift-set/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/p-success-achieved-new-year-gift-set-273508-m.webp]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>340.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/p-success-achieved-new-year-gift-set-273508-m.webp,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/p-success-achieved-new-year-gift-set-273508-1.webp,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/p-success-achieved-new-year-gift-set-273508-3.webp,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/p-success-achieved-new-year-gift-set-273508-2.webp,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/p-success-achieved-new-year-gift-set-273508-5.webp,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/p-success-achieved-new-year-gift-set-273508-4.webp,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/p-success-achieved-new-year-gift-set-273508-6.webp]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>442</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Professional Panache - Personalized Work Essentials Pen Set]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The Professional Panache – Personalized Work Essentials Pen Set is a sleek and stylish writing instrument designed for professionals who value elegance and precision. With its premium finish and smooth ink flow, it makes writing effortless and refined. Perfect for corporate gifting, client appreciation, or personal use, this pen set can be customized with names or logos to add a personal touch. It comes in a classic design that exudes sophistication, making it an ideal addition to any desk or office set.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Personalised Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/professional-panache-personalized-work-essentials-pen-set/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/pngimg.com-pen_PNG7402-1.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>50.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/pngimg.com-pen_PNG7402-1.png]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>485</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Premium Blue Dry Fruit Gift Box]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Elevate your gifting experience with this Premium Blue Dry Fruit Gift Box — a perfect blend of luxury and tradition. The elegant royal blue box features intricate mandala artwork and opens to reveal four gold-lid jars nestled on a soft satin base. Each jar is beautifully designed to hold a variety of premium dry fruits, ...]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 1500-2000</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/premium-blue-dry-fruit-gift-box-perfect-corporate-diwali-gift/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.52-1-scaled.jpeg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>2000.00INR</g:price>
			<sale_price>1800.00INR</sale_price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.52-1-1-scaled.jpeg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.52-2-scaled.jpeg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.52-scaled.jpeg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.53-1-scaled.jpeg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.53-scaled.jpeg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.54-scaled.jpeg]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>493</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Sea Green Dry Fruit Gift Box]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Our Sea Green Dry Fruit Gift Box is a refreshing and premium assortment of handpicked almonds, cashews, pistachios, walnuts, and other dry fruits, designed to bring health and happiness to any occasion. Packaged in an elegant sea green box, it makes the perfect Diwali gift, corporate hamper, or festive treat. Whether gifting clients, employees, or family, this hamper combines luxury, nutrition, and thoughtful presentation, creating an unforgettable experience for the recipient.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 1500-2000</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/sea-green-dry-fruit-gift-box/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-10-09-at-11.25.01-AM-scaled.jpeg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>2000.00INR</g:price>
			<sale_price>1800.00INR</sale_price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.56-scaled.jpeg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.56-1-scaled.jpeg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.56-2-scaled.jpeg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.57-1-scaled.jpeg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.57-scaled.jpeg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.58-1-scaled.jpeg]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>500</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Pink Dry Fruit Gift Box]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Our Pink Dry Fruit Gift Box is a charming and indulgent selection of premium almonds, cashews, pistachios, walnuts, and other dry fruits that bring both health and delight. Packaged in a vibrant pink box, it is perfect for Diwali gifting, corporate events, or special celebrations. Show your care and appreciation with a gift that is as nutritious as it is visually stunning, ensuring your loved ones, colleagues, or clients feel valued and special.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 1500-2000</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/pink-dry-fruit-gift-box/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.18.00-1-scaled.jpeg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>2000.00INR</g:price>
			<sale_price>1800.00INR</sale_price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:additional_image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.58-2-scaled.jpeg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.59-1-scaled.jpeg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.59-2-scaled.jpeg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.17.59-scaled.jpeg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.18.00-1-1-scaled.jpeg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.18.00-2-scaled.jpeg,https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/WhatsApp-Image-2025-09-24-at-18.18.00-scaled.jpeg]]></g:additional_image_link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>554</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Professional Notebook Gift Set]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This elegant Notebook &amp; Pen Gift Set combines style, functionality, and premium quality, making it an ideal choice for professionals, clients, or employees. The set features a high-quality notebook with ample pages for notes, journaling, or meetings, paired with a smooth-writing pen that adds a touch of sophistication to everyday tasks. Its black and gold design exudes elegance and professionalism, while the ready-to-gift packaging ensures a polished presentation without any extra effort. Perfect for corporate gifting, employee recognition, client appreciation, or office use, this set not only enhances productivity but also leaves a lasting impression of thoughtfulness and class.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Corporate Gift Hampers &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/professional-notebook-gift-set/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/WhatsApp-Image-2025-10-03-at-3.50.12-PM.jpeg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>210.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>557</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Executive Black Notebook & Pen Gift Set]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The Executive Black Notebook &amp; Pen Gift Set is a perfect blend of elegance and functionality, designed for professionals who appreciate style and practicality. This premium set features a matte black notebook with an elastic closure and a sleek metal pen with smooth ink flow, all presented in a sophisticated black gift box. Ideal for corporate events, conferences, promotional giveaways, business meetings, or employee recognition, it can also be customized with your company logo, making it a thoughtful and professional gift that leaves a lasting impression while enhancing your brand’s image.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Corporate Gift Hampers &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/executive-black-notebook-pen-gift-set/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/WhatsApp-Image-2025-10-03-at-3.50.11-PM-1.jpeg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>210.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>560</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Elite Trio Gift Set]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Make a lasting impression with this elegant 3-in-1 Corporate Gift Set, thoughtfully designed for professionals and business associates. The set includes a sleek metal pen, a stylish leather card holder, and a premium metal keychain, all beautifully packed in a classy gift box. Perfect for corporate events, client appreciation, employee recognition, or festive gifting, this set combines style, utility, and sophistication, ensuring your brand is remembered with every use.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Corporate Gift Hampers &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/elite-trio-gift-set/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/WhatsApp-Image-2025-10-03-at-3.50.10-PM.jpeg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>250.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>562</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Premium Pen & Keychain Gift Set]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This elegant Premium Pen &amp; Keychain Gift Set is a perfect choice for corporate gifting, client giveaways, or employee appreciation. The set includes a sleek, high-quality metal pen with smooth writing performance and a durable metallic keychain with a stylish finish. Packed in a premium black box, it offers a professional and classy look, making it ideal for business events, promotions, or personalized gifts.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Corporate Gift Hampers &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/premium-pen-keychain-gift-set/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/WhatsApp-Image-2025-10-03-at-3.44.23-PM.jpeg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>100.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>564</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Personalized Desk Organizer with Calendar, Clock, and Pen]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This Personalized Desk Organizer with Calendar, Clock, and Pen is a stylish and functional addition to any office or study space. Designed for both practicality and elegance, it features a sleek black finish with gold accents that add a touch of sophistication to your workspace. The organizer includes multiple compartments for pens and stationery, a built-in clock, and a calendar to help you stay on top of your schedule. It also features a convenient phone stand slot for easy access to messages and notifications while working. The nameplate can be customized with your name or company logo, making this organizer not only a useful desk accessory but also a thoughtful and professional gift for colleagues, clients, or loved ones.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Corporate Gift Hampers &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/personalized-desk-organizer-with-calendar-clock-and-pen/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/WhatsApp-Image-2025-10-03-at-3.44.23-PM-1.jpeg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>300.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>567</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Vacuum Flask Set with Bottles and Cups]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This vacuum flask set is a versatile and practical collection designed to keep your beverages at the desired temperature, whether hot or cold, for an extended period. Made from high-quality stainless steel and BPA-free materials, it is durable, rust-resistant, and safe for everyday use. The double-walled vacuum insulation technology ensures excellent heat and cold retention, making it perfect for travel, office, home, or outdoor activities. Each flask features a secure, leak-proof lid to prevent spills and maintain freshness, while the included cups offer convenient serving for various beverages. This set is an ideal and eco-friendly way to enjoy your favorite drinks anytime, anywhere.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/vacuum-flask-set-with-bottles-and-cups/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Vacuum-Bottle.jpeg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>250.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>574</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Milano Gift Set]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The Milano Gift Set is a perfect blend of sophistication, style, and practicality — designed to elevate everyday experiences with a touch of luxury. Crafted for professionals, executives, and those who appreciate fine quality, this premium set combines elegant design with superior functionality.
Each item in the Milano Gift Set is thoughtfully selected to complement modern lifestyles, making it an ideal choice for corporate gifting, festive occasions, and personal celebrations. Whether you’re expressing gratitude to clients, rewarding employees, or surprising a loved one, the Milano Gift Set leaves a lasting impression of class and care.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/milano-gift-set/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Milano-gift-set.jpeg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>340.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>575</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Modware Kohenoor Mini Combo Set]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The Modware Kohneer Mini Combo Set is a perfect blend of elegance and practicality. It includes a premium insulated casserole and a matching water bottle designed in a stylish gold and white finish. Ideal for keeping your food hot and beverages cold for long hours, this set ensures freshness and convenience wherever you go. Whether used at home, in the office, or during travel, it adds a touch of class to your everyday routine and also makes a thoughtful and functional gift option.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/modware-kohenoor-mini-combo-set-thegiftara/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Untitled_design-removebg-preview.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>340.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>579</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Portable Blenders]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Blend anywhere, anytime with this compact USB rechargeable mini blender. Featuring sharp stainless-steel blades, a leak-proof design, and one-touch blending, it’s perfect for smoothies, shakes, and juices on the go. Lightweight, stylish, and easy to clean — your perfect fitness and travel companion!]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/portable-blenders/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/WhatsApp-Image-2025-10-06-at-3.46.17-PM.jpeg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>290.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>615</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Golden Gleam of Diwali]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Celebrate special moments with elegance and sweetness through our Golden Delight Gift Hamper. Thoughtfully curated in a luxurious cream and gold round box, this hamper radiates festive warmth and sophistication.
It includes an assortment of premium chocolates, gourmet treats, a beautifully wrapped gift box, a golden floral tealight holder, and other delicacies — all wrapped with a satin ribbon for a rich and festive look.
Perfect for Diwali, corporate gifting, weddings, or special celebrations — this hamper adds a touch of golden luxury to every occasion.
Ideal for: Corporate gifting | Festive celebrations | Weddings | Special occasions]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 1500-2000</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/golden-gleam-of-diwali/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Golden-Gleam-of-diwali-.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>1978.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>618</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Budget-Friendly Diwali Corporate Hamper]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Celebrate every occasion with the Golden Delight Snack &amp; Sweets Hamper, thoughtfully curated to bring together taste and elegance. Packed in a premium Giftara Classic Magenta Sleeve Box, this hamper includes Navrattan Namkeen (130g), Kashmiri Shahi Mix (60g), Aloo Bhujia (50g), Cracker Chocolates (4 pieces), and a set of 2 Ladoo Candles. Perfect for festive gifting, this compact and beautifully presented box (23.4 x 18.7 x 6 cm) adds a touch of sweetness and style to every celebration.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 500-1000 &gt; under-1000</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/budget-friendly-diwali-corporate-hamper/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Budget-Friendly-diwali-Corporate-hamper.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>544.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
			<g:google_product_category>Home &amp; Garden &gt; Decor &gt; Home Decor Decals</g:google_product_category>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>623</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Diya	& Delight Box]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Celebrate the festive spirit with the Charcoal Delight Gift Hamper, an elegant blend of sweetness and charm. Beautifully packed in a GT Charcoal Dry Fruit Bouquet Box (15 x 15 x 15 cm), this hamper includes rich Doda Barfi (200g) and a stylish set of 2 T-light Holders in a GT Box. Perfect for Diwali, festive gifting, or special occasions, it adds a warm and luxurious touch to your celebrations.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/diya-delight-box/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Diya-Delight-Box.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>482.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>625</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Celestial Diwali Corporate Gifts]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Celebrate Diwali with this thoughtfully curated Giftara hamper that brings sweetness, tradition, and style together. It features 5 delicious chocolate crackers, 100g of natural and organic almonds and 100g of natural and organic cashews, each packed in charming potlis. The set also includes 2 hammered copper glasses for a touch of elegance and 2 beautifully painted terracotta diyas to light up your celebrations. All these items are carefully arranged in the vibrant and festive Giftara Diwali Raspberry Glace box (10 × 10 × 4 inches), making it a perfect gift to delight your loved ones and add joy to the festive season.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 1000-1500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/celestial-diwali-corporate-gifts/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Celestial-Diwali-Corporate-Gifts.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>1286.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>627</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Festive Cheers	& Treats]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This beautifully curated festive hamper features a blend of thoughtful and eco-friendly delights. It includes a set of two Mandala Printed Tin Candles that add a warm, aesthetic touch, along with a 60 gms pack of crunchy Aloo Bhujia for a savory treat. The hamper also features a set of four vibrant Rice Rangoli Test Tubes to brighten any celebration, eco-conscious Seed Crackers (Plant Patakhas) for a green twist on traditional festivities, and five delicious Choco Crackers to satisfy sweet cravings. All these carefully selected items come elegantly packed in a GT Midnight Cherry Blossom Box measuring 27 x 18.7 x 6 cm, making it a perfect gift for festive occasions.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 1000-1500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/festive-cheers-treats/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Festive-Cheers-Treats.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>1419.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>629</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Festive Flavours]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This festive hamper is a delightful blend of traditional flavors and handcrafted elegance. It includes 8–10 pieces (150 gms) of crispy Chakli, a timeless festive snack, paired with a pack of Shakarpara (200 gms) and Chivda Namkeen for a perfect balance of sweet and savory indulgence. Adding a touch of artistry, the hamper features a set of two beautifully painted terracotta diyas adorned with dried flowers—ideal for brightening up the festive décor. To complete the assortment, it includes Jaipuri Ghewars and Tikoni Mathri (80 gms), offering authentic Rajasthani taste in every bite. All these festive treasures are thoughtfully arranged in The Giftara Festive Box measuring 10 x 8 x 4 inches, making it a charming and elegant gifting choice for the season.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 1000-1500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/festive-flavours/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Festive-flavours.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>1074.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>631</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Festive Limelights in Lilac]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This beautifully curated hamper includes 200g of Kaju Katli elegantly wrapped in satin and adorned with dry flowers, a pack of soothing Lavender Dhoop Cones, 80g of crunchy Smoor Rice Crisps, and a healthy Signature Seed Mix featuring an assorted blend of nutritious seeds. All these items are thoughtfully arranged in a festive Gota Patti embellished top-bottom box measuring 10 × 7.5 × 3.5 inches, making it a perfect gift to celebrate special occasions with style and elegance.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 1500-2000</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/festive-limelights-in-lilac/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Festive-limelights-in-lilac.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>1743.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>633</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Mitti & Mithaas Hamper]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This exquisite hamper is a perfect blend of tradition and sweetness. It features 200 gm of delicious Doda Barfi, a classic Indian sweet, alongside a set of two handcrafted terracotta diyas, adding a touch of elegance and festivity. The Giftara Tilak Set, comprising roli, rice, mishri, and chandan, brings the essence of traditional rituals to your celebrations. All these thoughtful items are beautifully presented in GT’s All Things Nice Box (8 × 5 × 4 inches), making it a delightful gift that spreads joy, warmth, and the spirit of Indian heritage.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/mitti-mithaas-hamper/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Mitti-Mithas-Hamper-.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>403.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>636</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Regal Diwali Delights]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This delightful hamper features 200g of Moong Barfi, crunchy Smoor Rice Crisps, 2 Laddoo candle blocks, and 2 Laddoo-shaped candles for a festive touch. It also includes aromatic Tulsi Dhoop and 2 stylish carpet coasters. All items are beautifully arranged in a sage green Gota Patti embellished top-bottom box measuring 13 × 9 × 3.5 inches, making it a perfect gift for Diwali or any special occasion.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/regal-diwali-delights/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Regal-diwali-delights.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>2692.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>638</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Shubh Blessings of Diwali]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This festive hamper beautifully blends flavor, fragrance, and tradition. It includes a set of two Shubh Labh keychains in vibrant pink and yellow hues, symbolizing prosperity and positivity. The dried flower wax diyas (set of 2) add a warm, aromatic glow to any celebration. For a touch of indulgence, the hamper features Kashmiri Shahi Mix (60g) and Aloo Bhujia (60g)—perfect savory delights to complement the festive mood—along with five pieces of GT Midnight Cherry Blossom Choco Crackers for a sweet finish. All these charming treats are elegantly packed in a premium box measuring 27 × 18.7 × 6 cm, making it a thoughtful and delightful gift for any special occasion.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 500-1000 &gt; under-1000</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/shubh-blessings-of-diwali/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Subh-Blessings-with-Diwali-.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>684.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>643</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Shubh Deepawali Box]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This elegant festive hamper includes a set of 2 pink candle votives and Shubh Labh wall decor stickers to add a traditional touch. It also features a Lilac lotus pouch containing essential pooja samagri — incense cones, a pooja book, ceramic incenser, mishri, roli, rice, and chandan. Complementing the set is a blush pink pearl potli with 50g of premium cashews. All items are beautifully presented in The Giftara Festive Box (10 × 8 × 4 inches), making it a perfect gift for Diwali or special celebrations.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 1000-1500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/shubh-deepawali-box/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Subh-Deepawali-Box.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>1030.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>645</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Sweets Savory Festive Set]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Celebrate the festive season with this thoughtfully curated Giftara hamper. It features a set of 2 pink candle votives and Shubh Labh wall decor stickers to bring positivity and charm to your home. A lilac lotus pouch contains essential pooja samagri, including incense cones, a pooja book, ceramic incenser, mishri, roli, rice, and chandan. Adding a sweet and nutty touch, a blush pink pearl potli holds 50g of premium cashews. All items are elegantly arranged in The Giftara Festive Box (10 × 8 × 4 inches), making it a perfect gift for Diwali, special occasions, or as a thoughtful gesture for loved ones.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 500-1000 &gt; under-1000</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/sweets-savory-festive-set/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Sweets-Savory-Festive-set-.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>681.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>647</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Tea Triumphs For Fetes]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This chic festive hamper features 145g of Chia Dill Cookies, an elegant Dargel ivory glass with a golden festive foil design, and t-light lotus-shaped diyas to brighten your celebrations. All items are beautifully arranged in The Giftara Chic Circular Box (10 × 10 × 4 inches), making it a stylish and thoughtful gift for Diwali or any special occasion.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 1500-2000</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/tea-triumphs-for-fetes/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Tea-Triumphs-for-Fetes.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>1851.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>649</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Tyohaar Treat Box]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Celebrate the festive season with this beautifully curated GT Festive Lotus Box hamper. It includes 40g each of Pistachio and Almond Praline Brittles, offering a delightful mix of crunchy and nutty treats. The set also features 2 exquisitely crafted terracotta diyas and 3 rice rangoli test tubes, perfect for adding a traditional and vibrant touch to your celebrations. All items are thoughtfully arranged in the GT Festive Lotus Box (27 × 18.7 × 6 cm), making it an ideal gift for Diwali or any special occasion.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/tyohaar-treat-box/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Tyohaar-Treat-Box.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>498.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>654</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Warm Wishes of Diwali]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Experience the perfect blend of tradition, taste, and elegance with this thoughtfully curated festive hamper. It features 200 gm of premium Kaju Katli, beautifully wrapped in satin and adorned with delicate dry flowers, paired with Smoor Caramel Crisps (80 gm) for a touch of indulgence. A Golden Lotus T-Lite Candle Holder with a tea light candle adds a warm festive glow, while Artisanal Darjeeling Green Tea offers a refreshing, aromatic experience. The Giftara Tilak Set—complete with roli, rice, mishri, and chandan—brings a traditional touch to your celebrations. All these exquisite elements are elegantly presented in a Golden Gota Patti embellished top-bottom box (10 × 7.5 × 3.5 inches), making it a luxurious gift choice that radiates charm, culture, and festive spirit.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Festive Seasonal Gifts &gt; All</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/warm-wishes-of-diwali/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Warm-wishes-of-diwali-.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>2093.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>656</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Premium Eco-Friendly Notebook]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This eco-friendly gift set features a cork-covered notebook and a bamboo pen, elegantly packaged in a kraft paper box. Designed with sustainability in mind, the set combines natural materials with a minimalist aesthetic, making it ideal for professionals, students, or eco-conscious gift giving. The notebook includes an elastic closure for secure storage, and the smooth-writing bamboo pen complements its stylish, earthy look.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Corporate Gift Hampers &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/premium-eco-friendly-notebook/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Wodden-dairy-and-pen-.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>400.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>659</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Premium Black Corporate Gift Set]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This elegant Premium Black Corporate Gift Set is the perfect blend of style and functionality. It includes a sleek leather notebook, metal pen, card holder, and keychain — all thoughtfully arranged in a premium box. Ideal for corporate gifting, client appreciation, or festive giveaways, this set adds a touch of class to every occasion.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Corporate Gift Hampers &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/premium-black-corporate-gift-set/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/WhatsApp-Image-2025-10-03-at-3.52.52-PM.jpeg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>400.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>661</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Elegant Pen & Keychain Gift Set]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Add a touch of class to your gifting with this beautifully designed 2-in-1 Elegant Pen &amp; Keychain Gift Set. The set includes a premium matte-finish pen with smooth ink flow and a stylish metal keychain featuring a sleek, modern design — both crafted to complement each other perfectly.
Encased in a sophisticated black gift box, this set reflects professionalism and elegance, making it an ideal choice for corporate gifting, client appreciation, employee recognition, and festive giveaways. Compact yet impactful, it’s a thoughtful token that leaves a lasting impression.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Corporate Gift Hampers &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/elegant-pen-keychain-gift-set/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Key-chain-and-pen-.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>129.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>663</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Wooden Mobile & Pen Holder Stand]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[A stylish and practical desk organizer made from premium wood, featuring slots for pens, business cards, and your smartphone. Perfect for keeping your workspace neat and elegant.

Price: ₹300 | Custom logo engraving available]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Corporate Gift Hampers &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/wooden-mobile-pen-holder-stand/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Phone-Pen-holder.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>300.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>665</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Premium Cork Wallet & Keychain Gift Set]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This Premium Cork Wallet &amp; Keychain Gift Set is a perfect blend of elegance, sustainability, and practicality. Crafted from high-quality natural cork with a smooth PU leather interior, the wallet offers ample space with multiple card slots and a roomy compartment for cash, making it both stylish and functional. The matching cork keychain adds a coordinated touch and features a sturdy metal ring, ideal for daily use. Both items come beautifully packed in a sleek black gift box, making it an excellent choice for corporate gifting, special occasions, or personal use. The keychain can also be customized with your logo, adding a personalized and professional appeal to this eco-friendly and durable gift set.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Corporate Gift Hampers &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/premium-cork-wallet-keychain-gift-set/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Purse-and-key-chain.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>400.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>667</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Lucky Electric Mug with Smart Warmer Plate]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The Lucky Electric Mug with Smart Warmer Plate is an ideal choice for those who love to sip their coffee, tea, or milk at the perfect temperature. Made from premium ceramic material, this elegant mug comes with a lid and spoon for added convenience. The smart warmer plate keeps your beverage consistently warm, ensuring every sip is as fresh as the first. Its automatic temperature control feature provides both safety and efficiency, making it perfect for home or office use. With its minimalist design and smooth finish, this mug set also makes a thoughtful and stylish gift for family, friends, or colleagues.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 1000-1500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/lucky-electric-mug-with-smart-warmer-plate/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Mug.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>1299.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>669</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Eco-Friendly Cork Hardcover Notebook]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The Eco-Friendly Cork Hardcover Notebook combines modern elegance with sustainable design. Crafted with a natural cork cover, this notebook offers a soft, textured feel while promoting an eco-conscious lifestyle. It features ruled pages that provide a smooth writing experience, making it ideal for journaling, meetings, planning, or creative notes. The elastic band closure ensures your pages remain neat and secure, and the built-in ribbon bookmark allows easy navigation. Perfect for students, professionals, and environmentally aware users, this notebook adds a natural charm to your daily routine or gifting needs.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Personalised Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/eco-friendly-cork-hardcover-notebook/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Dairy-1.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>210.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>671</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Premium Stainless Steel Water Bottle]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Stay hydrated in style with this fashionable, insulated stainless steel water bottle. Designed to keep your beverages hot or cold for up to 20 hours, it’s perfect for daily use, travel, gym, or office. The sleek metallic finish and leak-proof cap with a carrying strap add both elegance and convenience. Durable, eco-friendly, and easy to clean — a smart choice for modern, on-the-go lifestyles.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/premium-stainless-steel-water-bottle/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Untitled-design-6.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>300.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>673</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Premium Vacuum Insulated Stainless Steel Bottle]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Stay refreshed all day with this double-wall vacuum insulated stainless steel bottle, designed to keep beverages cold for up to 24 hours and hot for up to 12 hours. The large-mouth design allows easy filling, pouring, and cleaning, while the leak-proof lid ensures no spills on the go.

Crafted with food-grade stainless steel, this bottle is 30% lighter yet tougher than ever, making it perfect for gym, travel, office, or outdoor use. The modern matte finish adds a stylish touch to your hydration routine.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/premium-vacuum-insulated-stainless-steel-bottle/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Untitled-design-1-1.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>299.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>676</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Elegant Stainless Steel Water Bottle]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Experience a perfect blend of style, simplicity, and durability with this sleek stainless steel water bottle. Designed for everyday hydration, it keeps your beverages hot or cold for long hours thanks to its double-wall insulated construction.

Its minimalist matte white finish gives a premium, elegant look — perfect for office, gym, school, or travel use. The lightweight and leak-proof design ensures easy carrying and spill-free convenience wherever you go.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/elegant-stainless-steel-water-bottle/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Untitled-design-6.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>399.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>678</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Stainless Steel Thermal Flask]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[This premium stainless steel thermal flask is designed to keep your beverages hot or cold for extended hours. With a double-wall vacuum insulation, it maintains the temperature of coffee, tea, or water for up to 12 hours. The sleek brushed steel finish gives it a modern and professional look, ideal for both office and home use.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 500-1000 &gt; under-1000</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/stainless-steel-thermal-flask/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Untitled-design-8.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>550.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>680</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Matte Black Thermal Coffee Carafe]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The Matte Black Thermal Coffee Carafe combines elegant design with superior insulation performance. Crafted with a double-wall vacuum stainless steel interior, it keeps beverages hot or cold for up to 12 hours. Its matte black finish adds a premium and modern touch, making it perfect for office meetings, cafes, or home use.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 500-1000 &gt; under-1000</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/matte-black-thermal-coffee-carafe/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Untitled-design-7.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>649.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>682</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Electric Kettle – Stainless Steel with White Finish]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The Stainless Steel Electric Kettle blends speed, style, and convenience in one elegant design. Crafted with a durable stainless steel interior and a sleek white exterior enhanced with chrome accents, it adds a refined touch to any kitchen or workspace. Powered by rapid heating technology, it brings water to a boil in just minutes—ideal for quickly preparing tea, coffee, or instant meals with ease and efficiency. Modern, practical, and beautifully designed, this kettle is the perfect companion for everyday use.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 500-1000 &gt; under-1000</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/electric-kettle-stainless-steel-with-white-finish/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Untitled-design-5-1.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>599.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>684</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Sleek Stainless Steel Water Bottle]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Stay stylish and hydrated with this premium stainless steel water bottle. Featuring double-wall insulation, it keeps drinks hot for up to 12 hours or cold for 24 hours. The sleek, rust-resistant design is lightweight, durable, and 100% leak-proof—perfect for travel, gym, office, or daily use. Eco-friendly and reusable, it’s a smart, sustainable choice for modern living and makes an ideal gift for any occasion.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 500-1000 &gt; under-1000</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/sleek-stainless-steel-water-bottle/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Untitled-design-6.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>525.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>700</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[White Rhino Stainless Steel Electric Kettle]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Boil water quickly and safely with the White Rhino Stainless Steel Electric Kettle. Crafted with a sleek, mirror-finish stainless steel body and ergonomic handle, it combines modern style with everyday practicality. Its efficient heating element ensures rapid boiling, while the automatic shut-off and boil-dry protection provide peace of mind. Ideal for tea, coffee, or instant meals, this durable and easy-to-clean kettle is a perfect addition to any home or office kitchen.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/white-rhino-stainless-steel-electric-kettle/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Untitled-design-4-1.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>380.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>710</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Travel Folding Electric Kettle]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The Quality of Life Collapsible Electric Kettle Set is a compact and portable appliance designed for travel, office, and small living spaces. Made with a food-grade silicone body and a durable heating base, it features a foldable design that saves space and makes it easy to carry. The set includes a matching collapsible cup, a detachable power cord, and a one-touch boil button for simple operation. It also comes equipped with automatic power-off and boil-dry protection for safety. With a capacity suitable for 1–2 cups of hot water, it’s perfect for quickly preparing tea, coffee, or instant meals while on the go.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 1000-1500 &gt; Watch and Buy</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/travel-folding-electric-kettle/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/WhatsApp-Image-2025-10-27-at-12.41.14-PM-2.jpeg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>1100.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>712</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Music Bird Aroma Diffuser]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The Music Bird Aroma Diffuser is a stylish and multifunctional device that combines aromatherapy, soothing music, and ambient lighting to create a relaxing atmosphere. Designed with an elegant bird-cage aesthetic, it features small decorative bird figures inside and emits a soft, calming light. The diffuser releases a gentle mist of fragrance to freshen the air while playing soft music for a peaceful experience. It is USB-powered, compact, and ideal for use in bedrooms, offices, or meditation spaces. This diffuser adds both beauty and tranquility to any environment.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 500-1000 &gt; under-1000 &gt; Watch and Buy</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/music-bird-aroma-diffuser/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/WhatsApp-Image-2025-10-27-at-12.41.15-PM-1.jpeg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>900.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>717</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[TripFactory Stainless Steel Vacuum Insulated Bottle]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The TripFactory Stainless Steel Vacuum Insulated Bottle is a sleek, durable, and travel-friendly bottle that keeps drinks hot for up to 12 hours and cold for up to 24 hours. Made from high-quality stainless steel with a matte black finish, it features a leak-proof lid, double-wall insulation, and a modern design. Lightweight, reusable, and eco-friendly, it’s perfect for travel, office, gym, or daily use.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/tripfactory-stainless-steel-vacuum-insulated-bottle/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Untitled-design-3-1.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>349.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>724</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Electric Mixing Mug]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The Electric Mixing Mug is a stylish and practical self-stirring mug designed to automatically blend your favorite beverages with just the press of a button. Featuring a sleek glass body, wooden handle, and matching wooden lid, this mug combines elegance with modern convenience. It’s perfect for making instant coffee, hot chocolate, protein shakes, or any powdered drink effortlessly — simply add your drink powder, pour in hot water, and let the mug do the mixing for you.
With its built-in automatic stirrer, it ensures a smooth, lump-free drink every time while saving you time and effort. The transparent design allows you to see the blending process, adding a touch of sophistication to your daily routine. Ideal for home, office, or gifting, the Electric Mixing Mug makes beverage preparation easy, mess-free, and enjoyable.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500 &gt; Wedding &amp; Anniversary</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/electric-mixing-mug/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/DSC04053-min_1600x.webp]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>349.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>822</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Digital Wooden Alarm Clock with Wireless Charger]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Enhance your bedside or office setup with this sleek modern wooden LED alarm clock — a perfect blend of style, technology, and practicality. Crafted with a premium wood-grain finish, this clock adds a touch of warmth and sophistication to any décor while keeping you on time and connected.
Designed with both elegance and functionality, it clearly displays the time, temperature (°F/°C), and features a built-in Qi wireless charging pad compatible with all Qi-enabled smartphones, earbuds, and other devices. Simply place your device on top for effortless, cable-free charging.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 500-1000 &gt; Graduation &gt; under-1000</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/digital-wooden-alarm-clock-with-wireless-charger/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Wirless.webp]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>900.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>824</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Pickup Dynamic Humidifier]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Experience cleaner, fresher air with the Pickup Dynamic Humidifier, your perfect home or office companion for creating a comfortable and healthy indoor environment. Designed with modern technology and sleek aesthetics, this humidifier ensures optimal humidity levels while adding a touch of elegance to any space. Built to enhance your daily comfort, the Pickup Dynamic Humidifier uses ultrasonic mist technology to deliver a fine, cool mist that quickly balances the moisture in the air.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Budget 1000-1500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/pickup-dynamic-humidifier/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/51129a21-f03f-493e-aaa3-bf7abd0ee773.webp]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>1180.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>834</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Pickup Anti-Gravity Dynamic Humidifier]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Experience a new level of innovation and relaxation with the Pickup Anti-Gravity Dynamic Humidifier, a cutting-edge device that combines modern technology, visual artistry, and practical functionality. Designed to elevate your home or office environment, this humidifier not only moisturizes the air but also mesmerizes you with its anti-gravity water droplet display — a stunning illusion that makes water appear to flow upward.
Using ultrasonic mist technology, it emits a fine, cool mist that refreshes your space, balances humidity levels, and helps relieve dryness in the skin, throat, and sinuses. Its whisper-quiet operation ensures a calm and comfortable atmosphere, perfect for sleep, work, yoga, or meditation.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Birthday &gt; Budget 500-1000 &gt; under-1000</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/pickup-anti-gravity-dynamic-humidifier/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/637dca79170b3008d74d69bb-anti-gravity-water-droplet-humidifier.jpg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>900.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>841</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Small Portable Juicer (Multi-Function Blender)]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The Small Portable Juicer is a stylish and multi-functional mini blender designed for people on the go. With a 400 ml capacity, stainless-steel blades, and USB rechargeable battery, it easily blends smoothies, juices, and shakes anytime, anywhere. Its compact, lightweight design makes it perfect for home, office, gym, or travel use. Simple one-button operation and easy cleaning add to its convenience. A smart and useful choice for daily use or thoughtful gifting — perfect as a modern wedding return gift or corporate gift.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/small-portable-juicer-multi-function-blender/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Untitled-design.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>299.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>844</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[LED Digital Mirror Alarm Clock]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The LED Digital Mirror Alarm Clock is a modern and multifunctional timepiece designed to add elegance and convenience to your daily routine. Featuring a sleek mirror-finish LED display, it clearly shows the time, temperature, and alarm settings, making it perfect for your bedroom, office, or study desk. With adjustable brightness, a snooze function, and USB or battery power options, it combines style with practicality. The mirror surface also doubles as a mini makeup or desk mirror, enhancing its usability. Compact, stylish, and easy to use — it’s an ideal choice for home décor, corporate gifting, or wedding return gifts.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/led-digital-mirror-alarm-clock/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Untitled-design-1.png]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>400.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>846</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Leakproof Insulated Stainless Steel Bottle with Handle (1200ml)]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Stay hydrated in style with this Leakproof Insulated Stainless Steel Bottle, designed for both comfort and durability. With a large 1200ml capacity, it keeps your beverages hot or cold for hours, making it perfect for daily use, travel, gym sessions, or office work.
The double-wall vacuum insulation maintains the ideal temperature, while the ergonomic handle ensures a secure and comfortable grip. Its leakproof lid comes with a built-in straw for convenient sipping, whether you’re on the move or relaxing at home. Crafted from premium stainless steel, it’s rust-resistant, easy to clean, and built to last.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Home Lifestyle Gifts &gt; All &gt; Under 500</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/leakproof-insulated-stainless-steel-bottle-with-handle-1200ml/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/leakproof-insulated-stainless-steel-bottle-with-handle-black-1200ml.webp]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>500.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
		<item>
			<g:id>915</g:id>
			<title><![CDATA[Customized Mugs]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Add a personal touch to your daily coffee ritual with our premium customized mugs. Designed for professionals and teams, these mugs can be personalized with company logos, employee names, or motivational quotes — making them ideal for corporate gifting and events.Durable, stylish, and dishwasher-safe, they’re the perfect blend of functionality and branding.
Ideal for: Employee appreciation, client gifts, event giveaways.]]></description>
			<g:product_type>Personalised Gifts &gt; All &gt; Birthday &gt; Under 500 &gt; Wedding &amp; Anniversary</g:product_type>
			<link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/product/customized-mugs/?utm_source=pinterest&utm_medium=social]]></link>
			<g:image_link><![CDATA[https://thegiftara.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-10-at-4.11.14-PM.jpeg]]></g:image_link>
			<g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
			<g:price>100.00INR</g:price>
			<g:mpn></g:mpn>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>